PETER ADEBISI

Lagos | +234 8133754026 | Peterkunle90@gmail.com

Profile Summary

An outstanding and detailed, proactive sales officer with over 4 years of experience with success in developing products and businesses, increasing sales and also cultivating strong relationship with customers, which has contributed to ground breaking achievements over the years. I am Persistent and competent with theoretical and practical knowledge in Business administration aim at meeting customers' needs and contributing positively in achieving the team's goals. Adept at maintaining efficiency and delivering excellent support to team and clients

Work Experience

School Liaison Officer **Dufil Prima Foods Plc** March 2023 - Current Lagos

Surulere,

- Resolved long-standing customer complaint, resulting in the retention of a high-value account by 18%
- Oversaw a challenging sales team of 11 representatives to achieving double-digit sales growth in Q1 for 2024 which resulted in 25% team's performance.
- Coordinated 36 delivery vans which led to 20% increase of supply of stocks to distributors and sub distributors in 2 regions.
- Developed and delivered sales presentations to key product managerial team heads and decision-makers on strategic sales, resulting in 12% growth in revenue.
- Trained 15 newly employed sales representatives in sales ethics, product knowledge and organizational culture, resulting in 25% achievement of individual sales targets.

Sales Representative **Dufil Prima Foods Plc**January 2021 – February 2023

Lagos

Surulere,

- Optimized sales processes that reduce the sales cycle time by 25%, improving customer satisfaction and increased sales velocity.
- Led a marketing campaign that increased brand awareness by 60%, resulting in a 35% increase in Indomitable packs across 2 district regions in Lagos.
- Recognized as the top sales performer for three consecutive quarters, contributing to a 26% rise in sales for the entire year.
- Created a competitors report which was used by managers for product analysis and this led to 12% delivery in new product within 4month.

Office Assistant

Dufil Prima Foods Plc

January 2017 – December 2020

Surulere, Lagos

- Provided administrative support to multiple departments, contributing to team productivity and seamless communication
- Pitched the description and report on Omnibiz application work flow which brought about enhancing precision and efficiency among team members by 25%.
- Leveraged on data-driven insights to analyze consumer trends, significantly enhancing inventory management. This led to a 20% decrease in overstock and a 10% boost in sales.
- Managed and gained over 120 new major customers across 2 regions which increases customers retention by 18%.
- Resolved over 40 customer complaints with a 45% resolution success rate, contributing to improved customer satisfaction.

Education

September 2019 – February 2022 Lagos State Polytechnic, Lagos	HND (Business
Administration)	
February 2014 – February 2017 Yaba College of Technology, Lagos	OND (Business
Administration)	

Skills

- Product knowledge
- Learning and understanding prospects language.
- Proficient in managing sales volume
- Openness to learn and understand new concepts and technologies.
- Familiar with sales tools and technologies
- Team management and Leadership
- Marketing and competitors' research
- Proficiency in Microsoft office ,Zoom, Google meet and Outlook etc

Certification

The Ultimate Microsoft Excel (Udemy)

Business Analytics: Decision-Making using Data Analytics, Power Bi and Ai Skills (Fulleryield)